http://www.ghosttownmuseum.com/privacy

Privacy policy
Your privacy is important to us. Much of the specific information requested within our site is voluntary and need not be submitted by the visitor. If personal information is submitted as part of a request for information, it is used to investigate or respond to the request. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to meet your request. We do not release or sell information for the purpose of a third party’s marketing program or solicitations.
Types of information collected on GhostTownMuseum.com
We collect personal data when you order our guides or sign up for our newsletter, which includes first and last name, email address and mailing address.
Navigation information
Each time you visit Colorado.com, anonymous navigation information is collected by our servers. This information includes:
• the type of browser and operating system you are using;
• the address of the referring site (ie the previous site you had visited) and the website you leave our site to visit;
• the date and time of your visit;
• your server’s IP address (a number which is unique to the machine); and
• the address of the pages you accessed.
This provides GhostTownMuseum.com with information about how the website is used and navigated, including the number of hits, the frequency of visits and the duration of visits to each page on the site. It does not personally identify individual users.
How we collect personal information offline
Personal information will only be collected by lawful and fair means, for one or more specified purposes, which are relevant to GhostTownMuseum.com’s operations. When personal information is collected directly from the individual to whom it relates, the purpose of collection will be identified and it will only be collected with the person’s consent.
Information collected on this site may also be combined and de-identified to provide GhostTownMuseum.com with anonymous demographic and usage information. GhostTownMuseum.com can then use this aggregated information to develop new and/or more appropriate content to our users.
In addition, anonymous navigation information may be used for statistical analysis of the site, for marketing purposes and to tailor the content of the site to the needs of GhostTownMuseum.com users. Statistical information is not disclosed in connection with your personal information.
Cookies
Currently GhostTownMuseum.com does use “cookie” technology. Cookies were originally designed to help a website distinguish a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your email address.
We use cookies so that we can provide personalized information that we believe will be of value to you based on preferences you have indicated while visiting the site. You will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept the cookie. You may opt-out of these features here.
When we disclose personal information
GhostTownMuseum.com works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your guide efficiently. In this case the information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies we contract with safeguard your personal information in accordance with GhostTownMuseum.com’s policies.
Personal information collected at this site will only be disclosed to third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and with the terms and conditions of any relevant service. You should check the terms and conditions of individual products and services for information about disclosures.
Security
We make our best efforts to ensure that our systems are secure. GhostTownMuseum.com safeguards the security of the data you provide to us with physical, electronic and managerial procedures.
Disclaimer
While all attempts have been made to ensure the accuracy and reliability of all materials contained within this website, we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Information on businesses and organizations within the GhostTownMuseum.com website is provided by those organizations and is not verified or endorsed by Ghost Town Museum. GhostTownMuseum.com expressly denies any guarantee of the accuracy or reliability of information published on the site and shall not be held responsible for any losses caused by reliance upon the accuracy or reliability of such information. User shall use information obtained through the Internet at own risk and is encouraged to call individual businesses to verify prices, amenities, features, dates and all other important details before traveling.
There are adventures and activities featured in this website that carry significant risk of personal injury or death. We do not recommend that anyone participate in these activities unless they are fully aware of the risks and are willing to personally assume all responsibility associated with those risks. GhostTownMuseum.com and the Ghost Town Museum are not liable for incidents or accidents arising from information we provide in this website.
I grant the Ghost Town Museum permission to use any or all of my information for web usage. Content may be edited for placement.
Copyright 2017 All Rights Reserved, Ghost Town Museum
Reproduction in whole or in part of any photographs, maps and illustrations without prior written permission from the copyright holders is strictly prohibited. Users are granted permission to view or print information on this website for travel planning or personal use and may distribute this information to friends, family members or personal acquaintances for travel planning or personal use.
© 2020 Ghost Town Museum. All Rights Reserved. Website design by Kettle Fire
X
Head on over, y’all! We're open and following all local and state guidelines to give you a safe and enjoyable visit.
